So that's where you were hiding, boss.
Found you.
Thank God.
Guess that's gonna be your new body.
I can remember when my soul
slipped away before I conked out.
You told me that you had to go, that
you would make it right, I believe.
As long as you're in the game, that you'll
bring it all home for the both of us.
But still, I miss you.
It would mean the world
if you'd call again,
boss.
Thank you so much for watching.
I can't stand in fear,
but I'll be the same day.
The hope is that the end of the
year, the future will be known.
I'll be the same way,
and I'll be the same way.
I'll be the same way, you know.
So, from their eyes,
they'll be the same way.
The Wrecking The End.
Wow, wow!
Nessuno può scegliere il destino scelto.
Roman solo il risultato
che voi sarete distrutti.
L 'eterna Zoom esiste solo per me.
Puoi cantare canzoni di
tristezza nel Monday senza tempo.
Let's go.
The time has come take the arrow and
impel your stand the hell he did a
180 he's coming in real hot trono
you have to try and stop him now it's
too far i can't you've got to be
kidding what are you waiting for it's
because you've got the arrow just my luck
it had to crap out now The arrow! Quickly!
Let go of it!
It's a good thing I thought to swipe
that stupid Kotz Beretta just in case.
But what the hell, bullets?
None of you told me my
revolver was in such bad shape.
What if it was the boss who broke it?
You idiot!
Feet before opening that
big mouth, number five!
Look around, moron!
There ain't nothing here but air!
so how could the boss even touch us? Huh?
I didn't see anyone near us
when the darn thing broke.
It's metal fatigue.
You've been using it too much.
It's totally normal.
Look, the damn crane's giving out.
All this fighting with no
maintenance can't be good for it.
Hey!
Give me a break.
How many more times am I
gonna have to shoot your ass?
Wait, it's my life he's after now.
Simply having the arrow
back is no longer enough.
Golden wind!
Yes, of course, Requiem now seeks to punish
me because I dared to touch the arrow.
Mister, run!
A little help, guys?
Where's my reload?
That isn't a revolver!
We're gonna need a new magazine!
In my tank, it's longer than usual!
It's no use!
I'm...
Journal!
Got something for you!
I'm gonna throw it! Go wide!
Goddammit!
Hey, Mr. Polnareff!
He looks fine, but still, how did...
Mista, take a moment to think back on
what I said to you at the Colosseum.
I confess to not fully grasping
the extent of Requiem's powers.
That has now changed.
With his true plans in motion,
he's lost interest in me.
What do you mean his true plans?
They're unfurling before your very eyes.
I'm beginning to mutate!
That's why Requiem gave up on chasing me!
This is but the first
stage in his grand plan.
His intentions weren't
merely to swap our souls.
He seeded our transformation
into completely new beings!
The prelude is over.
Now comes the crescendo.
Whether or not I live is irrelevant.
The history of the world
has unfolded on its
own path for four and
a half billion years.
Requiem will thrust it on a
new one in a matter of hours.
Fascinating.
The true nature of his
powers has been laid bare.
Crazy, children.
Your help has been most invaluable to me.
The path forward is finally clear.
With nothing left in my way
the arrow will soon be mine and
it's all thanks to you what the
hell is happening to these people
his powers insane you said
this is happening everywhere it
doesn't look like it's causing
them any sort of pain at least
they've all got blank stares
in their faces but even so I
can't shake the horrible thought
that my body's gonna mutate
this can't be real right am I
seriously gonna mold piece by
piece until there's nothing left
of me trish i i'm fine i think
there's no stopping the process now
in a few short hours we will all have
finished our damnable mutations then we
better not waste even a second let's get a
move on you did this you just had to
touch the arrow didn't you defeat diavolo
my big fat hairy stinking ass all the
arrow has done is and send our life to us.
That's enough.
There's no way in hell he
could have foreseen this.
We must refocus and figure
out how to take down Requiem.
That's right, run to him you fools.
Move in nice and close.
I can feel the remainder
of his secrets unraveling
faster and faster with each step you take.
Let me seize the power of the arrows
so the world may grovel at my feet.
We've almost got him.
Good.
Everybody stand still right now!
That's it!
Stay far apart!
And don't move a muscle! What?
I told you to freeze, Mista!
We'll have to catch up with Requiem later!
What the hell, Giorno?
You trying to get us killed?
In case you haven't
noticed, my body's melting!
I took a closer look at your revolver.
The one you said just broke,
something's off about it.
The broken piece doesn't fit quite right.
That shouldn't be the case.
If it really were Metal Fatigue,
the pieces would fit perfectly.
Giorno, what exactly are you saying?
I need you to stay in place too!
Trust me, I know what I'm talking about!
Hey, asshole!
Requiem's getting away!
If the bullets say it's cause
the stupid gun gave out,
then that's what frickin' happened!
End of story!
Besides, it got me the sweet Beretta now!
The two pieces don't fit right,
cause a chunk probably fell off!
That's possible.
But it's far more likely
to be something else.
We'll know for sure as soon
as we get that lost piece.
Let's take a look, Golden Wind.
I gave part of the gun
life and let it run loose.
It's blind, but its
nose makes up for that.
It can pick up things our eyes might miss.
Little guy just proved it.
He's found a critical
piece of this puzzle.
Dude, come on! Forget them all!
I already told you, it's impossible
for another person to have done this.
So drop it.
Bullets and I aren't stupid.
We know what we're talking about.
Nobody got anywhere close to me
when the damn revolver broke.
But that's it.
There's no one here.
That's why we're standing apart.
Remember, his range is just a few meters.
Giorno, are you?
No one got anywhere close to
Narancia when he was killed either.
No one besides any of us.
Mr. Polnareff,
if it really is as you say And the boss
does turn out to possess two personas.
That means his soul could
reside in anybody he chooses!
My guess, Diavolo is hiding
out inside one of us? What?
Just think about it Why hasn't Trish
been able to sense him this whole time?
And that's not the only thing.
He's also waiting for us to
die doing his dirty work!
Do you get it now?
He's the reason why your gun broke
Come on!
Stay right where you are, Mista!
I'll tell it again!
We have to remain out of his range!
I'm the one whose gun
was destroyed, moron!
And the person closest to it was you, too.
There's no way it's me!
Wait, hold on.
Right before Narancia
got killed, let's see.
The closest one was...
Merda!
I have to act quickly!
Requiem is about to slip from my grasp!
Churno Chuvana, you pestilent brat!
He's inside one of us,
that's all I know for sure.
What might not be obvious is we've
got him backed into a corner.
Diavolo might be able to
sic Emperor Crimson on us,
but he still can't completely
control his physical host.
If he did have that kind of freedom, there'd
be no need for him to use subterfuge.
He'd just finish us all off.
It's exactly because he's so constrained
that we're all still standing here alive.
We have the upper hand.
Let's not waste this chance.
What if it's the turtle?
He was the only one around
me when my revolver broke.
So it's gotta be Polnareff
who got possessed!
That can't be the case.
In case you've forgotten, Requiem
almost killed him just now.
and only because the
boss broke your weapon.
The boss wouldn't risk letting
injury befall his physical host.
Besides, I can only
sense one soul in there.
He's a singular turtle
with only one spirit.
You can discern souls? That's good.
There's a catch.
If I can't make direct
physical contact, then no.
How does that even work?
Life energy comes in clusters.
Direct touch tells me how
many souls in a clump.
No other way.
I'll have to touch each
of you briefly to know.
There still remains one problem.
What if you fall within the boss's range?
I've got a trick for that.
Mr.
Polnareff kindly taught it to me earlier.
I just have to look for a
sudden increase in blood drops.
That'll tell me if time has left.
that might help you detect him but
the rest will all be on you the
fates be willing you might just be
able to narrowly dodge his strike
look it's definitely not
me how I mean there's
no way I was the furthest
person from Narancia
why don't I just examine
you first and get it
over with what you You
can stop right there!
Don't come any closer!
Stay back!
What if Diavolo's hiding in you, huh?
Then what happens?
By the time Narancia died,
his body was an empty shell.
I know because my soul could travel
seamlessly into it, nothing stopped me.
That's why I'm sure it's just me in here.
Well gee that's a super
reassuring story is
what i'd say if i had
any way of confirming!
It's true i mean come on
how could you know for
sure the boss isn't actually
hiding somewhere in?
There it doesn't look like you can check
yourself with that ability can you vista if
you keep this Up we can
kiss the arrow goodbye
stop or you'll kiss your kneecaps goodbye?
Stop it now!
You can check me first, Giorno.
Come on, just do it!
We've wasted too much time on bickering.
It's just like you said.
We should seize the chance to hit
the boss while he's vulnerable.
There's no other way. Let's go.
We must proceed quickly.
Someone's dying. I know it.
If we move closer...
Turtle it was Mista the boss was
hiding inside him spicy lady first.
Oh, he wasn't you
But horrifying speed he was able to close
the distance in nearly no time at all.
Sweet daughter,
I've been waiting for this moment
your stand finally appears before me!
My Trish, had you not foolishly
revealed your stand to me?
your dear friends may very well
have succeeded in their gambit.
Release her at once!
As long as your stand is in my grasp,
I fear you're little more than a
puppet enslaved to my every whim.
He's going for a strike.
Brace yourselves, quick!
Time is about to...
Huh?
Where is he?
Did he forget to murder us first?
Why is he running away?
It's likely we're not at the
top of his list right now.
His focus seems to be
on seizing the arrow.
It's the only real thing that
matters, and he knows it.
Shoot him, Mista.
He can't be allowed to reach it first.
Pull the damn trigger!
A few bullet wounds are nothing
compared to what he will do.
I know the problem is.
I've already shot him.
I counted fired all six shots.
That bastards messing with time as he's
running if he sees him coming my bullets?
I just can't touch him!
After him!
It's all over if he gets that arrow!
That shadow, it must hold the key
to the arrow's imperviousness.
Let's see if my theory
proves to be correct.
Requiem's shadow always
extends in the direction?
Opposing my movements, regardless
of the sun's actual position.
That must mean...
To that man's eyes, the shadow should
appear as if it is stretching toward me.
But to Bucciarati, the shadow is
extending in front of Requiem itself.
In other words, the position of the shadow
depends on the position of the observer.
Cretanous Jade, your
powers are no mystery.
I understand how you manipulate souls.
Requiem is the silhouette of the soul.
To face it is to contend with
the shadow of one's own mind.
Therefore, attacking it is futile.
It's akin to attacking oneself.
If I eliminate this shadow,
the arrow will be mine.
Well, then, wherever a shadow treads,
a source of light must also be nearby.
He still hasn't gotten the arrow.
Go for Brokemista!
The only place it could
be is behind my soul!
He struck something behind his
head, yet Requiem suffered the blow.
What the hell happened?
You're mine at last.
Behold, the final victor
is I! I don't care.
Even if Diavolo somehow gets his vile
hands on the arrow, the fight goes on.
We'll just improvise.
Lucky for me, the blood he spilled when
he severed my arm is just ordinary matter.
No different from anything else.
Now ain't that right, Golden Wind?
It's showtime!
What's happening, that damn mongrel?
Not too bad.
I gotta catch up with them quick.
Fire again, mister!
Don't let him get too close!
Yeah, I know!
Gotcha!
Bet you didn't predict
that, you freakin' idiot!
Deflect the bullets comin'
at you all you want!
You can't do jack shit
about these other guys!
All right, fellas!
Y 'all flick that baby back to Papa!
He just launched a whole person!
All the way toward the arrow!
So he did predict our trajectory!
He used the body to course correct!
Did you truly believe,
even for a moment,
that your laughably slow wits could ever
hope to overcome my predictive mastery.
There are no flaws to exploit, as
I'm sure you've recently learned.
However, Bucciarati, you and your
gaggle did manage to make me try.
I never imagined you would be foolish
enough to betray your own Family,
nor did I believe you competent
enough to discover my true identity.
But, I'm grateful this path has led
me to the true power of the arrow.
Fate never fails!
A fitting reward for ones who have
conquered the adversity of their past!
Guys, Reload, don't just stare!
We already told you!
That magazine takes us a
little bit longer to refill!
Shit!
We're all gonna die!
No, what now?
Spicy lady.
Surprise!
You didn't deflect squat.
The bullets bounced.
My secret?
I turned them to chewing gum.
They stretched out thin as they flew, but
they clung to your fists the entire time.
Then they sprung back to me and threw you.
Trish, how long were you awake?
I too will conquer my past.
I refuse to be afraid, to
live in fear of my fate.
I won't run from it.
If it gets in my way, then I'll climb.
It's as simple as that.
The arrow! You guys!
It's so damn close!
Holy crap, I almost got it!
Kiss my ass, Diablo.
Go ahead and warp time or predict stuff.
It won't change a thing.
The arrow's coming to me, baby.
My dear girl, how I wish I had never
brought you into this wretched world.
Seems I've yet to break free of my past.
Curse it, worm.
Now, I'm angry!
No, it can't.
What was it you said about fate?
You just climb, am I right?
Well, I hope you like flying instead.
There you go.
Trash!
Come on,
I'll see this alive We are the
power Who's in the future Cause
we are the fighters Just
fighting for the rise Let's fight
Let's fight
Thank you.